The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives a magicless boy named Asta.
This brave young hero devotes blood, sweat, and tears
to becoming the next Wizard King.
Though Asta's situation is practically unheard of,
there are others residing in this kingdom
who possess at least a tiny amount of mana,
yet can barely use spells at all.
They make up a very small minority,
living their lives in the shadows.
But, like everyone else,
they do their best to survive.
I'm so sorry to hear you.
The nichts Addir школAS
天使と悪魔が交際してく
winter comin'
世界は矛盾だらけさ
abandoned 트럭
想い通りじゃない
そのくらいで הג're free
You shine like a diamond
Let's turn back time for a moment
Poor girl
Damn those magic knights
What's her condition?
She appears to have cracked several ribs
Shall I prepare some pain medication?
Yes, you could use some
Here you are
Thanks, I appreciate it
Here, drink
The pain should eventually subside
Okay
So what should our next move be?
Master Kabwe?
What exactly do you plan to do?
I'm going to kill the prisoner
No, not yet!
There are more important things that we need to worry about right now
Like that book?
It needs to be dealt with too
Lest our sacrifices be in vain
Wait, dealt with how?
They say that the devil dwells in the five-leaf clover
Let us be rid of this accursed book at once
Master Kabwe, please!
Why are you trying to stop me?
This wretched thing
It couldn't possibly be of further use to us
Wait
I don't really care about what you do to me
But Austin needs that book
So give it back
What a selfless request
But when such words come from lips tainted by forbidden magic
Well, I'd be a fool to listen
Siona, what's going on?
Siona, is she dead?
Onabi!
No
Damn you
Why betray us?
Have you still not put it together?
I'll say it plainly
The last thing we would want is to see the devil banished
We are the devil believers
We are an order that worships the devil
That can't be true
How can anyone worship such pure evil?
No
You asked us to help you destroy the devil
If not that
And what did you need us for?
You speak like we came to you as supplicants in need
But we simply took advantage of your hatred for the devil
In what way?
Well, seeing as you have access to the magic parliament
You've been privy to knowledge that was kept from us peasants
In addition to that, it's helpful to have someone who can actually use magic
Since we're dealing with the magic knights
Someone who can use magic?
What are you talking about?
Right
For somebody like you, it must be difficult to fathom
That there are people like us
Who are all but spurned by mana
One hot summer day
The neighborhood kids asked me to do a favor for them
They asked me to use my catalyst magic
To mix both of their magics together
So we could all cool off
They seemed truly happy
And seeing their faces made me feel happy too
But then I overheard them talking behind my back
And they said they were only acting like my friends to impress the adults
Since I didn't have any real friends
They said it was because I could barely use magic
She's so creepy
Then they just laughed
People like us have no place in this kingdom
We've been told that since we were children
You think this will help you?
We do
Before now, it's been like we didn't even exist
But no more
Despite the fact that he doesn't have a single drop of magic in his blood
Asta wields power equal to that of any great mage
By means of a grimoire that hosts a devil
So we'll imitate him
We'll do whatever we must to obtain the devil's might for ourselves
I will not allow that to happen
Why you?
Let's go
Right?
No
I can't let it end like this
I'll find a way
We're listening
Where are you?
It's a lie
These people aren't trying to bring about the devil's demise
Not at all
The truth is that
They're after the devil's power
What do you mean?
This organization actually worships the devil
They're called devil believers
Chairman Damnazio
I'm sorry
I was a fool
You must stop them
Please, sir
For all of us
What's wrong, Cobway?
Report
Do you mind filling us in on the details?
A devil-worshipping cult, huh?
Called the devil believers?
I don't think your subordinates would help that kind of group knowingly
It's safe to assume that they were being used under false pretenses
Those gullible idiots
I get wanting to destroy a devil
But who the hell would decide to worship one?
These people are a bunch of sickos, if you ask me
Excuse me
We traced the communication magic back to its source
And it would appear to have come from Tulio
Well, that's a surprise
Julius?
I order the Black Bulls to travel to Tulio
Apprehend these devil believers
And save Nero from their clutches
You got it
He must have used the last of his strength
To grab that thing so he could contact his former boss
Was it an argument gone bad?
No, there'd be signs of a struggle
These guys didn't have a chance to fight back
So they just slaughtered their own people?
It's like Chairman Chinmole said
They were being played for fools
They thought they were fighting a devil
Guess they must have outlived their usefulness
Captain
So creepy
A venomless viper
Powdered long-necked soft-shell turtle
And the root of a goikabuto plant
These ingredients are all quite difficult to come by
And knowing that
We can assume that the potion
Which put my best friend Asta to sleep
Was likely made here
As were the potions used at the execution site
I would love to get more information
On the person who lives here
But the local villagers
Seem to be pretty wary of us
I can help you with that, sir
Granny Maggie?
It's me
Oh, hi, Gordon
You brought some friends, eh?
This is Granny Maggie, everyone
We got to know each other
And became friends the last time we were here
How goes it, Granny?
My name is Asta, ma'am
It's an honor to meet you
You're way too loud
So are you, Magna
Hold on
Where's that mean-looking boy
Who called me an angel?
Don't tell me you came all this way
And didn't bring him
An angel?
Oh, if you mean my best friend, Ghosh
He's back at the capital
Watching over his little sister
Ah, well, it's a relief to hear
He was able to find the poor girl
Right?
I hate to rush this cute little reunion
But can we pick your brain for a bit, Granny?
We need info on the person who lives in the forest on the outskirts of town
You're talking about Bo?
Yeah, probably
We need you to tell us everything you know about Bo
It's real important
I can do that
But the next time you come around
You bring that broody young ghost fellow with you
Oh, you got it
She can barely use magic?
It's not actually all that rare
Though, I bet it seemed that way to you, Noelle
You can't really blame her
I mean, every single member of her family is good at magic
And Asta can't use it at all
And she knows he's a freak
This is all your fault
My fault?
But
Bo is also a wonderfully skilled apothecary
We don't go to a mage with recovery magic when we fall ill in this town
Herein tool you the sickling goes straight to Bo with her expertly made medicine
I could tell she was skilled just by looking at her shelves
I hear she worked hard to become that good
Perhaps we're all lucky she couldn't use magic
Because that's what drove her to develop such a skill
Kind of sounds like a certain meathead I know
Come to think of it, you might want to hear about Bo's good friend Dozzy
She lost both her husband and mother-in-law when those devil servants attacked the town
Where can we find her?
Like Bo, Dozzy can't really use magic
But she never let that get her down
She's a wonderful girl who's been through a lot
You'd better be nice to her if you meet
She got along very well with her husband V-Day
The two of them were as happy as any couple I've seen
Her husband's mother, Meishu, would always talk about what a wonderful daughter-in-law she was
Yami!
Hmm?
I think you should take a look at this, sir
This woman
Oh yeah, I've seen her before
Something's not right about this
Well, think about it
The old lady was just going on and on about how Dozzy and her husband were deeply happy
But that face looks pretty dead inside
Hang on
Why would someone whose family was killed by a devil become one of the creeps who worships a devil?
Nice work
You're on the right path, just keep flipping over rocks until you find some worms
Yeah, about that
Honestly, I have my doubts
And why is that?
The trail's getting kind of cold is all
I don't suppose you have any other intel we can go off of?
Nothing solid
I will say that the devil believers sought out people with the magic parliament in hopes of getting sensitive information from them
With that in mind, they likely know that the devil Megicula is in the spade kingdom
And that information probably factors into their plans
So what, you think they might want to offer Nero as a gift?
Huh
That reminds me, they still have the kids' grimoire too
How could you forget something that important?
Right
They probably wanted to give you and the grimoire to Megicula as some kind of package deal
Once they pay tribute, they'll defect to the spade kingdom
Or rather the devil inside it
Okay, but why?
I doubt we can answer that question without asking these people in person
But in any case, we can expect these cultists to start moving north
To reach the border, they'll have to cut across the Forsaken realm
Right, good luck
Thanks
Look sharp, dumbasses
We're moving out
Yes, sir
A mission?
That's right
I can't
Neglecting your duties, you must enjoy disappointing your sister
Old hag
Just what do you think you're doing here?
I think you know
I'm here to rescue Marie from her obsessive good-for-nothing brother
No, my angel stays here
What happened to her before was a fluke
I can guarantee Marie's safety now
Now get over yourself and go do your job
Shut your mouth, old hag
There's no job that's more important than watching over Marie
And have you given any thought to what would make Marie happy?
Magic knights are supposed to keep people safe, right?
I was so proud when I found out my big brother was going to be a magic knight
But I want to keep being proud of you
So please, Ghosh
I'll listen to you this time, but don't get used to it
I'm trusting you, so you had better not put Marie in danger again
Get your ass over here
She'll be safe with me
And so, the black bulls began their pursuit of the devil believers
Who had thought to have fled into the forsaken realm
In case this thinking had been an error
The other magic knight squads were sent out to search the common realm far and wide
But no matter how diligently the magic knights searched
They had no luck finding the devil believers
And several days passed with no progress
We've trekked through half the forsaken realm chasing these jerks
But we haven't caught so much as a whiff of their mana yet
It's possible that they're using some kind of devices to keep their mana concealed
The other squads haven't found anything noteworthy either
At this point, I would assume they've passed the forsaken realm
And are bound for the spade kingdom's border
Sounds about right
We've come across a few signs that they passed through ahead of us
Signs?
Yeah, bunch of weird crap
The locals at this village are not a whiff of their mana yet
It's possible that they're using some kind of devices to keep their mana concealed
The locals at this village say a bunch of their people disappeared too
It's happening everywhere we go
Do you think these devil whatevers are behind it?
That'll be my guess until I hear a better one
Hey, I got a question for you guys
Why the hell is everybody so determined to avoid us?
It's due to what happened with the eye of the midnight sun
Huh?
The people of the forsaken realm have had it quite rough
Almost everyone here feels like the magic knights left them high and dry
And at least a few of these people believe that the magic knights were behind the attacks
I'll do what I want
You can't make me stay
Please don't do this
Stop trying to keep me here, you've already made me late to the meetup
Everyone else is already there, I have to leave right now
You think they'll heal your leg with the devil's power?
Do you know how ridiculous that sounds?
Why would you think that's possible?
I don't think it is, I know it is
I mean, there's a guy who doesn't have any magic at all
And with the devil's powers he was able to get into the magic knights
But the boy was put on trial for using those powers
What do I care?
Once I have the devil's powers, I won't have to be scared of trials or anything else
Now let me go!
No, don't! Someone stop him, please!
What the? Hold it right there!
Hey, you had better explain why your mother's on the ground, now!
Just let go of me, I have to leave right now, no matter what!
They're all waiting for me just outside of town
Yep, we're making our way from Hikairo straight up to the border
There are two big rivers that blow into each other there, is that right?
Yeah
I don't see any people though
Well...
This is proof that we're still on their trail at least
Hey, you're not letting what that kid said bug you, right?
Oh, come on Magna, do I look like I'm upset?
Yeah, you do
How do I put this?
That poor kid's really struggling with his legs, so it makes sense that he would do anything to try and heal it, right?
And these devil believers are preying on that
Or at least pretending to be a ray of hope for people like him
These people have nowhere left to turn, they've run out of options
So we'll take a deal too good to be true
Yeah, well anyway, we've got to do something about them, fast
The area past Breed Mountain heading toward the Spade Kingdom has some volatile mana
The weather tends to get real rough
Odds are, they'll probably have to stop and wait it out
Roger that
There's backup on the way
But I want you three to race ahead and scout them out
We can't let them cross the border, understood?
Sir!
Nero
Oh crap!
Whoa!
Come on Magna, can't you fly this thing any steadier?
You're kidding me, right?
It's gonna be pretty difficult to catch them, if they manage to make it past Breed Mountain in this weather
Look down there, I think I see them!
Huh?
How are there so many? This is insane!
законnor
枕
OVER
Thank you.
I'll see you next time.
We've finally caught up with them, and they really are heading to the Spade Kingdom.
Black Clover, page 147.
Prepared to die.
We can't wait for reinforcements!
Don't worry, Nero.
We'll save you!